so let's see if we can figure out a raid
1 array suppose we have a raid 1 array
with two disks and for a single disk we
have a 200 gigabyte capacity 10
megabytes per second throughput and the
MTTF of a hundred thousand hours in that
case our two disk raid 1 array has a
data capacity of how many gigabytes a
throughput of how many megabytes per
second
assuming that we do equal numbers of
reads and writes
and finally our MTTF is equal to how
many hours and for this type of array we
also need to know whether we replace
failed disks or not
so here assume that we do replace the
failed disk and at the mean time to
repair meaning the mean time it takes us
to replace the failed disk is 24 hours